#### ryanmillerux.com

# Ryan M Miller

## **Experience Designer**

linkedin.com/in/ryanmatthewmiller ryn.m.mllr@gmail.com (303) 501-7861 Loveland, CO

Focused on solving problems and crafting intuitive, inclusive, and quality solutions for products that provide a simple and delightful experience centered around user needs, validated by research and testing.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **UX / UI Designer**

CNH Industrial, Remote | Dec 2022 - Present

· Cloud applications team for precision agriculture technologies

## **User Experience Designer**

In-Situ Environmental, Fort Collins | Feb - Dec 2022

- Created user personas adopted by the R&D department as an internal resource
- Built an interactive UI style guide for Developers to reference for design consistency and overall quality
- Lead functional and visual design efforts on multiple features and enhancements for both the mobile and web app

## **Digital Product Designer**

CGI, Denver / Remote | Jun 2021 - Feb 2022

 Assisted in design and research efforts on an innovative browser application for First responders provided by a prominent telecommunications company

## **Industrial Designer**

Angel Armor, Fort Collins | Mar 2017 - Jun 2021

## **Designer**

Taphandles, Seattle | Feb 2015 - Mar 2017

## **Industrial Design Consultant**

Medtronic, Boulder | May 2014 - Feb 2015

#### **EDUCATION**

## Certificate, UX / UI Design Bootcamp

University of Denver

Mar - Sep 2021

## **B.S. Industrial & Product Design**

Metropolitan State University of Denver

May 2014

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Hard Skills**

Planning and Discovery

**User Story Mapping** 

Sketching & Wireframes

Hi-Fi Comps / Task Flows

Rapid Prototyping

**Usability Testing** 

**Delivery Documentation** 

#### **Soft Skills**

Collaborative

Dependable

Empathetic

Adaptive

#### **TOOLS**

Figma, Adobe (XD, Illustrator,

Photoshop), InVision, Mural,

Microsoft Office, VS Code

#### **INDUSTRY**

UX / UI Design

Agile Software Development

Front-End Development

Industrial Design

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

**Design Patents Pending** 

Angel Armor, 2019 & 2021

Employee of the Year

Angel Armor, Dec 2018

**GDUSA Package Design Awards** 

Taphandles, Dec 2016

Design Patent US D756,817

Medtronic, May 2016